Gabriela Garín Palma

Full Stack Developer

Santiago, Chile | +56 9 7780 4013 | gabriela.garin@gmail.com | github.com/gabasaura linkedin.com/in/gabriela-garin

Profile

Fullstack Developer with experience in graphic design. Studied visual and multimedia arts. Confident in drawing, image composition, and color skills. Hands-on experience in UI/UX developing websites with WordPress, HTML, CSS, and jQuery.

Currently focused on backend and frontend development, applying technical knowledge to create efficient and effective solutions in an integral manner.

Available to contribute to frontend and backend programming. Motivated to continue learning and growing professionally. Interested in bringing creativity and dedication to challenging projects, collaborating, and being part of a team.

Skills

Python | Javascript | ReactJS | REST/API | Flask | Git | Github | SQL | SQLAlchemy | PostgresSQL | SQLite | HTML5/CSS3 | Bootstrap | Wordpress | Scrum | Adobe PS / AI

Education

4Geeks Academy, Full Stack Developer *⊗*

Mar 2024 - Jun 2024 | Santiago, Chile

UNA Universidad Nacional de las Artes - Multimediales,

2021 - 2022 | Bs As, Argentina

Multimedial Arts

UNA Universidad Nacional de las Artes - Visuales,

Visual Arts, specializing in drawing.

2018 - 2021 | Bs As, Argentina

INACAP, Professional Graphic Design

2006 - 2011 | Santiago, Chile

Instituto Chileno-Britanico, English Advanced

First Certificate Exam Approved

2003 - 2005

Professional Experience

Graphic Designer / Illustrator, Freelance ⊘

2014 – present | Remote

Experience as a freelancer, creating a variety of graphic pieces, specializing in illustration and web development using HTML5/CSS3 and WordPress. Proficient in image design, with a strong track record of close collaboration with entrepreneurs to develop brand concepts and visuals.

Graphic Designer, Mural

Dec 2020 - Dec 2021 | Remote

Development of templates for Mural web app on demand, primarily for marketing and creative meetings.

Web Developer, Mediadiv

2014 – 2015 | Santiago, Chile

Building websites with HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, and WordPress.

Intern / Junior Graphic designer, Mancha Diseño

2011 - 2012 | Santiago, Chile

Developed various graphic assets, including editorial materials such as reports. Contributed to the creation and maintenance of websites using Adobe Flash, HTML, and WordPress. Experienced in layout and design.

Projects

Pipo App, Frontend Development (Deploy on RENDER) *⊗*

May 2024

Web App: Directory of public restrooms in the city. Allows users to comment, rate, and add new locations. **Technologies used:** ReactJS | HTML5/CSS3 | Bootstrap | React-Leaflet | Python | Flask | PostgresSQL

Languages

Spanish — Native │ English — Advanced